Jolly old St. Nicholas, lean your ear this way
快乐的圣诞老人  耳朵凑过来
Don't you tell a single soul what I'm gonna say
接下来我说的话  千万别公开
Christmas Eve is coming soon, now, you dear old man
平安夜即将到来  亲爱的老人
Whisper what you'll bring to me, tell me if you can
请你悄悄告诉我  会带什么来
Jolly old St. Nicholas
快乐的圣诞老人
Whatcha gonna bring to me?
你会带什么给我
Is it a stash of gems that I can eat all day and night?
是一大堆够我吃上一辈子的宝石
Or is it a diamond ring that I can give to Rarity?
又或一枚钻戒让我向瑞瑞表心意
When the clock is striking twelve and I'm fast asleep
时针指向十二点我在深梦里
Down the chimney broad and black, with your pack you'll creep
烟囱下你宽又黑  弯腰的身影
All the stockings you will find hanging in a row
挂成排的长袜里  你将会看见
Mine will be the shortest one, you'll be sure to know
最短的那只是我的  你肯定知道
Come and give me those Christmas presents
快把我圣诞礼物带来
Don't make me wait no more
别再让我等待
Give me some presents
带给我礼物
Come give it to me, Santa, yeah!
快带来给我  老人  耶!
Pinkie Pie wants a candy hat and Applejack wants to cook
萍琪派要顶糖果帽  而阿杰想要下厨
Rainbow wants a lightning chain and Twilight wants a book
云宝要闪电项链  而暮暮要本书
Rarity wants a set of lace and Fluttershy wants a nest
瑞瑞要一组花边  而小蝶要鸟巢
Now choose for me, dear Santa Claus, what you think is best
帮我选选  圣诞老人  啥礼物最好
Jolly old St. Nicholas
快乐的圣诞老人
Whatcha gonna bring to me?
你会带什么给我
Jolly old St. Nicholas
快乐的圣诞老人
Whatcha gonna bring?
你会带什么
Whatcha gonna bring to meeeeee?
你会带什么给我?
Yeah!
耶!
翻译
轮回
校对
森林金雨  Loadhe
润色
包子
背景图绘制
缤纷彩彩
时间轴
蛟龙  Loadhe
制作
习成 PBU 工作组
感谢观看